incpak.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy - INCPak

INCPak.com is Independent News Coverage Pakistan – INCPak Group website. Please know that while using this website and/or submitting information at this website you are volunteering the same; you are informed of the way such information may be used and you agree to such use.

 **Information you submit**

To avail certain services and offerings, to participate in certain activities and to make contributions at this web-site you may be asked to submit personally identifiable information such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, your opinion on issues and items and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At times you may also be submitting information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at this website include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of this website, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products / programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site’s activities and offerings.

You may also be submitting certain non-personally identifiable information such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider.

 **How We Use the Information**

The information you submit will be used by us for communication and contact, to fulfill your requests, to respond to inquiries and to offer other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you or to the person whose information you submit to us.

We may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us and We use the non-personally identifiable information that you submit to improve our website.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or summon. We may also disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that you submit will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy policy (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you.

 **Cookies & Web Beacons**

To enhance your experience with our website, our web pages may use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand website usage and to improve the content and offerings on our website. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us.

“Web beacons” or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use web beacons on this site from time to time for this and other purposes.

Cookies and web beacons shall be deemed to be information submitted by you to us.

 **Collection of Information by Third-Parties**

Our website may contain links to other websites whose information practices or policies may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

This website may offer content (e.g., contests or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may have access to personally identifiable information that you may submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties’ use of such information. The site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will have access to such information.

This website may use a third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see on a web page. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to facilitate such advertisements and their effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies.

 **Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

 **Access to Information**

Access to personally identifiable information that is submitted to our website may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of submission.

 **For users under 18**

If you are aged 18 or under, please get your parent/guardian’s permission before using this website and before submitting any information.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may [Contact Us](http://www.incpak.com/contact/ "INCPak Contact Us") or Email us [incpak@gmail.com](mailto:incpak@gmail.com)

 **Updates & Effective Date**

We may update or amend this privacy policy from time to time. You are advised to review this policy each time you use this website.

INCPak.com
